<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Live Or Die</string>
    <string name="key_name">name</string>
    <string name="live_or_die_title_page">Live Or Die Title Page</string>
    <string name="start_your_destiny">START YOUR DESTINY</string>
    <string name="page0">While sitting in the basement like you are ever so accustomed to, you realize something has happened that has never before.  The door opens behind you and you see a glowing light call you by name, " %1$s are you ready to be reborn?"</string>
    <string name="page0_choice1">Talk to glowing light.</string>
    <string name="page0_choice2">Hide under the bed!</string>

    <string name="page1">You begin speaking to the light and ask it to clarify the meaning of his statement... he then reaches to your forhead and expands your mind.  You realize your life lived in the darkness was no life at all, but merely your present reality.  He asks if you want to explore truth... what do you say to it...</string>
    <string name="page1_choice1">I want TRUTH!</string>
    <string name="page1_choice2">I am happy in the darkness, it\'s all I\'ve ever known.</string>

    <string name="page2">You run and hide under your bed which evermore surrounds you in the all to familiar darkness, the ever so bright light walks towards you and rips the blanket from your face and asks again if you are ready to be reborn.</string>
    <string name="page2_choice1">You decide to go with him.</string>
    <string name="page2_choice2">You yell leave me alone I dont want to be reborn, leave me be in eternal darkness.</string>

    <string name="page3">He takes you up the stairs of the dark basement you have lived at your entire life.  You first walk into an empty room with a treasure chest at the center.  The light disappears and you walk towards the chest and open it.  What did you find in it?</string>
    <string name="page3_choice1">Knowledge</string>
    <string name="page3_choice2">Pleasures</string>

    <string name="page4">You find knowledge in the treasure chest and realize you have lived in darkness you whole life and want to search for truth all the days of your life.  How does the story end?"</string>
    <string name="page4_choice1">Happy Ever After</string>
    <string name="page4_choice2">You leave your knowledge there and run back under your bed.</string>

    <string name="page5">You continue to search and find new truths all thanks to your pursue of it.  You look back to time in the darkness and your ignorance to reality.  You feel a new knowledge entering your being, new thoughts flood your mind and the light begins to open your understanding to a new reality which leaves your new found light, looking like a dimming candle...</string>
    <string name="page5_choice1">Cool Story</string>
    <string name="page5_choice2">Cool Story</string>

    <string name="page6">You find more pleasures than you could ever need.  You begin to enduldge for many years of your life until your age slows your ability to enjoy many of them, you start to regret finding the pleasures and wished it could have been something more real, something which brought truth and realization instead of something which ultimately brought nothing.</string>
    <string name="page6_choice1">Boring Story</string>
    <string name="page6_choice2">Boring Story</string>
    <string name="story_page_image">Story page image</string>
    <string name="play_again_button_text">Play Again</string>

</resources>
